<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>/home/j4ckofalltrades</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/</link><description>Recent content on /home/j4ckofalltrades</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 21:42:31 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jduabe.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/projects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 14:56:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/projects/</guid><description/></item><item><title>blog.init()</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/posts/blog-init/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 21:42:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/posts/blog-init/</guid><description>This is a short write-up of how I got this blog up and running. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of options available out there &amp;ndash; from ready-to-go blogging platforms to building your own site with a static site generator &amp;ndash; I went with the latter option using Hugo and hosting it on GitHub Pages.
Being able to just write stuff in Markdown and not having to worry about styles and layouts (my design skills leave much to be desired) were the main reasons for going this route, not to mention the services you can use to host your blog for free.</description></item><item><title>Hacktoberfest 2020 Retrospective</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/posts/hacktoberfest-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 12:50:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/posts/hacktoberfest-2020/</guid><description>This one&amp;rsquo;s long overdue and when the swag arrived last week I figured I really need to get this done.
The past year has been tough to say the least and getting to write code for fun while helping out the open-source community was a very welcome distraction.
Though I have been programming for a while this was my first time participating in Hacktoberfest and contributing to open-source in general, it was nice to get to talk to and interact with maintainers and other like-minded individuals who are passionate about code and giving back to the community.</description></item><item><title>Bio</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:26:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/about/</guid><description>Jordan Duabe &amp;mdash; @j4ckofalltrades I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer, Linux geek, and command-line ninja from the 🇵🇭, currently based in 🇦🇺.
The majority of my work experience has been writing code for web and mobile apps in a variety of programming languages and frameworks, but I&amp;rsquo;ve also worked on DevOps-related stuff like setting up server environments and CI/CD pipelines.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not writing code &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m either playing DotA or gaming on the Switch, tinkering with Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s, or learning to play the ukulele.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:25:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Happy Halloween 🎃 🦇 👻
Obligatory first post while getting everything set up; this website is powered by Hugo with the hugo-coder theme and is hosted on GitHub Pages.
More posts in the coming days (or weeks), stay tuned.</description></item></channel></rss>