<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>75% on /home/jordan</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/tags/75/</link><description>Recent content in 75% on /home/jordan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jduabe.dev/tags/75/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ID80 build</title><link>https://jduabe.dev/posts/2022/id80/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jduabe.dev/posts/2022/id80/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/j4ckofalltrades/image/upload/c_limit,w_900/v1642946766/keebs/id80/id80_lxezxv.jpg" alt="keeb">&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Sized just right at a 75%—a compact configuration to feature the top function row — the ID80 mechanical keyboard kit from IDOBAO makes a great fit on any desk. This board is both durable and easy to build. Its PCB also features Kailh hot-swap sockets, which allow users to quickly change switches without a soldering.
Featuring a seamless case design made from anodized aluminum, it also incorporates an integrated plate which holds switches in place. QMK programmable for custom key commands, and outfitted with a USB-C port for fast connectivity, this board is ready for work or play.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>The 75% is a very popular keyboard layout, in part to its aesthetic and also functional &amp;ndash; just a tad bit wider than a 65% but with a full function row. The function row is especially enticing to me as most IDE shortcuts require function keys, and I don&amp;rsquo;t really use the arrow keys or the navigation cluster all that much.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I went for a clean, simple aesthetic for this build; an all black build with the aluminimum case and &lt;strong>ePBT Black on White&lt;/strong> keycaps.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Used the highly rated &lt;strong>Boba U4T&lt;/strong> switches, and &lt;strong>Durock v2&lt;/strong> stabilizers for this build, both lubed with &lt;strong>Krytox 205g0&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Custom keymap not too far off from the default / standard 75% layout, just had a couple of small quality of life modifications:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Soft escape (Esc when help, Ctrl when tapped)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Media controls on layer 1&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>